NATASHA CARR

natashacarr1@yahoo.com | 07581080113 | natashacarr.github.io/portfolio

"Natasha is approachable, a great team player and communicator, creative and works well under pressure."

- Polina Palonova, Senior Cash Associate - Tory Burch

SUMMARY

Hello! My name is Natasha, and for the last eight years I have been working in retail operations. I am a **creative**, **organised** worker bee based in Buckinghamshire (but up for hybrid working), and I am now looking to use my educational and personal project experiences to get into a **web development** role.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- I won a design commission for my university's Student of the Year awards, resulting in a ceremony designed around my work.
- I had a book cover design chosen by the author, which was published and sold online and in bookstores.
- I designed a logo for an arts and design centre in Newport Pagnell, which was used for their company stationery and correspondence.
- I have been awarded 'Employee of the Month' on three occasions, across two different roles, for my organised and diligent work.
- I achieved my stores highest audit rating by managing the preparation of 70,000 units of stock, as shown by a 98% accuracy score.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

BSc (Honours) in Computing and IT

April 2020 - Present, The Open University

I am currently studying part-time toward this degree, with the intent to pursue a route in web design, covering topics so far such as Python, networking, Linux, robotics, and mathematics.

Codecademy Modules

October 2020 - October 2021

- HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript
- o jQuery and React
- o PHP, Python and Java

Microsoft Technology Associate Certification

October 2021

Completed the MTA: Introduction to Programming Using HTML and CSS exam.

Foundation Degree in Graphic Design

September 2010 - June 2012, University of Bedfordshire

I completed several design commissions during my studies and had some of my work exhibited in Centre:MK for an arts show.

SKILLS

JavaScript and jQuery

React JS

Python

HTML5 and CSS3

Coding environments

Problem solving

Organisation

Creativity

Teamwork

Communication

INTERESTS

Superhero movies (DC Marvel)

Quilling

Stand-up comedy (watching, not performing)

NATASHA CARR

natashacarr1@yahoo.com | 07581080113 | natashacarr.github.io/portfolio

WORK HISTORY

Sales Associate - Lidl UK

January 2021 - Present

Part-time Covid role to help fund my studies, processing early morning deliveries to the store.

Senior Stock Associate - Tory Burch

September 2018 - September 2020

I was promoted to Senior Stock Associate after eight months with the company, managing the stock team and keeping the stockroom functioning at its best.

- o Ensured stockroom ran smoothly in the high-pressure environment of a Bicester Village 'Top Five' store
- o Decided and delegated the days tasks to stock associates, training the team where needed
- Communicated effectively through radio to find stock for customers fast and efficiently

Community Associate - Regus

January 2018 - September 2018

Short term role at Regus, in which I was focused on customer care and safety whilst presenting a **friendly** face to clients and their visitors.

- Managed office facilities, handling client queries and issues
- Set up office space and services for new clients
- o Maintained site standards and arranged contractor visits where needed

Senior Operations Associate – Superdry

October 2015 - December 2017

As the highest ranked member of the operations team I had taken on the responsibilities of the Operations Manager for the last year after climbing to the highest associate tier in just eleven months.

- Worked quickly and accurately under pressure to ensure all jobs were done
- Accepted and processed deliveries, ensured recalls were completed accurately and before their deadlines
- Maintained the stockroom to high standards, reorganising stock where needed

Supervisor - Tiger

April 2015 - August 2015

Short term role at Flying Tiger Copenhagen, in which I opened multiple stores around the UK.

- Improved warehouse efficiency through setting and maintaining standards and training staff
- Ensured stock discrepancies were resolved and system entries were accurate and up to date
- o Created daily rotas and assigned jobs and areas to suitable staff members

Store Operations Associate – British Home Stores (BHS)

October 2012 - April 2015

I participated in the set up and opening of this site, and when required, took responsibility for cash management procedures. I was also named 'Most **Organised** Associate'.

- Created new procedures to improve stock storage and management
- Trained and supervised store associates in stockroom and cash management
- Managed and/or assisted in producing reports and updating cash management